By the end of this course, you've learned
neurodiversity describes the idea
that people experience
and interact with the
world around them in
many different ways.
There is no one right
way of thinking, learning,
and behaving, and differences
should not be viewed as deficits.
You learned that the neurodiverse
population remains a largely untapped
pool of talent, and they have the
ability to bring in new perspectives.
You learned that neurodivergent employees
are proven to have better pattern
recognition and creative thinking than
their neurotypical counterparts.
Plus, accommodating
neurodivergent candidates
can greatly improve
a company's image.
You learned that people managers must
practice inclusive recruiting with,
for example, psychometric
assessments or performance-based
tests, so as not to miss
out on neurodivergent talent.
You learned that leaders must accommodate
neurodivergent employees by creating
distraction-free workspaces, providing
flexibility, and educating themselves
and their team about the challenges and
uniqueness of people on the spectrum.